Hello everyone and welcome to my first cosplay inspired video and I'm going to show you the
Black Widow cosplay today. The Marvel character from all the Iron Man, Avengers movies whatever.
I ordered this cosplay so I did not like kind of craft it myself but it has a lot of details and I
I came up with the idea to do this because I did a photoshoot a couple of years ago
and everyone commented under this picture that I look like Black Widow.
I mean my hair was a bit shorter but I was wearing a black latex catsuit and a corset
and people kept coming back to me with the suggestion to make a Black Widow cosplay
and this is my first attempt here.
The key piece is of course the catsuit.
This is the catsuit.
It is so comfortable because I have to admit it I ordered a made to measure costume.
I'm not 100% satisfied with the fit and the shoulder area but the rest is so great and
it's keeping me warm and it's super cozy.
accessories came with it and I have to figure out which one is going to sit where.
I think there's a belt.
I had to adjust that a bit, it was a bit confusing but it kind of fits now.
second belt
I'm a bit worried about the shoe situation here because these ones were
too shiny I found other ones although I don't like the shoe cover here I don't
it's too wide it stands away from the shoe here so honestly I think it's going
to look better if I remove this boot cover I mean it's a nice idea but it's
not working here last parts the gloves and another accessory
They're a bit too wide and I think these ones are supposed to be like munition belts.
At least they keep the arms and the gloves together.
Done.
evaluate for a second here. I think the overall look is super cool. I probably am
going to wear this for Carnival because it looks cool, it keeps me warm and I
try to do some curls like Scarlett Johansson as Black Widow. By the way I love
her in this role and yeah. Apart from that I really like the catsuit with the
fit. I'm not really satisfied with all the accessories to be honest. I mean
let's be real for a second. I bought this at Aliexpress. I still paid $170 so it
was not too cheap and of course you can't compare it with real cosplay. I mean
all the great cosplayers they put a lot of work and hours in their costumes and
this is just no comparison here. It's okay for the money but I think some
parts are not really thought through like the shoe covers and this weird belt
which is way too long but you can't see it because I tried to squeeze it in
between here and stuff like that. So in general I love this look it is rather
cool and badass. I think the jumpsuit is really great concerning the fit so worth
the money. If you like see it as a whole it's really okay especially as I'm not a
cosplayer and this is like an attempt to buy not the cheapest costume out there
but a rather middle-priced costume with a lot of details. Yeah I wouldn't look too
close-ended details but in general it's really cool so I'm really okay with it I
think the look is rather good and I feel like I have to do some action posing
stuff oh yeah and of course I'm missing guns here but point one I don't own any
guns except Nerf guns, point two I think YouTube doesn't like guns that much
Me neither. Of course I want to take some pictures and as I already mentioned
action poses I think I'm going to go outside and do a little more
sophisticated and more actual posing than inside here.
Thank you.
Now I think I'm done here with all the action outside.
Tell me in the comments if you like this cosplay costume whatever if you like
this video what you think of it and yeah I hope you had fun I really enjoyed this
going to do some more cosplay videos in the future so keep an eye out for them
have a nice day see you around bye